    [
        {
            "question": "When was Mardi Gras invented?",
            "choice1": "March 3, 1699",
            "choice2": "May 8, 1765",
            "choice3": "August 22, 1888",
            "choice4": "November 10, 1705",
            "answer": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Who celebrates Mardi Gras the most?",
            "choice1": "Venice, Italy",
            "choice2": "New Orleans, Louisiana, USA",
            "choice3": "Rio de Janeiro, Brazil",
            "choice4": "Mobile, Alabama, USA",
            "answer": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "What do the colors of Mardi Gras stand for?",
            "choice1": "Love, happiness and sacred",
            "choice2": "Hope, value and richness of life",
            "choice3": "Faith, power and justice",
            "choice4": "Grass, sun and flowers",
            "answer": 3
        },
        {
            "question": "What does Mardi Gras mean?",
            "choice1": "Big party",
            "choice2": "New Orleans",
            "choice3": "Parade",
            "choice4": "Fat Tuesday",
            "answer": 4
        },
        {
            "question": "Where was the first known celebration of Mardi Gras held?",
            "choice1": "Mobile, AL",
            "choice2": "Biloxi, MS",
            "choice3": "Corpus Christi, TX",
            "choice4": "New Orleans, LA",
            "answer": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "How many king cakes are sold every year in New Orleans?",
            "choice1": "5,000",
            "choice2": "2 million",
            "choice3": "25,000",
            "choice4": "750,000",
            "answer": 4
        },
        {
            "question": "Since when Mardi Gras has been a legal holiday?",
            "choice1": "1990",
            "choice2": "1875",
            "choice3": "1905",
            "choice4": "1850",
            "answer": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Before the Cajuns settled in Louisiana, where did they settle after leaving France?",
            "choice1": "Maine",
            "choice2": "Florida",
            "choice3": "Eastern Canada",
            "choice4": "The Great Lakes",
            "answer": 3
        },
        {
            "question": "Which of the following is a Louisiana dish?",
            "choice1": "Gumbo",
            "choice2": "All of these",
            "choice3": "Jambalaya",
            "choice4": "Étouffée",
            "answer": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "What does it mean to get the baby in your piece of king cake?",
            "choice1": "Wealth and riches",
            "choice2": "Lucky in love",
            "choice3": "Absolutely nothing",
            "choice4": "Good luck all year",
            "answer": 4
        }
    ]